(Howard:)Really? Tell that
to the bathroom scale,
(Howard:)'cause one of you is lying.
(Bernadette:)Fine, forget I asked.
How was dinner at your mom's?
(Howard:)Awful. I had to rub her ointment
all over her again.
(Bernadette:)Why can't she do it?
(Howard:)Cause we've got a deeply
unhealthy relationship.
(Howard:)Which reminds me,
(Howard:)do you think you can get
any samples of this from work?
(Howard:)This was supposed
to last her a month,
(Howard:)but they didn't take into account
the square footage of her back.
(Bernadette:)Let me see.
(Bernadette:)How long have you been
putting this on her?
(Stuart:)I don't know.
Few weeks. Why?
This is really strong estrogen cream.
(Bernadette:)Please tell me
you've been wearing gloves.
(Howard:)Like these swollen sausages
could fit in gloves.
Howie, the estrogen's
getting absorbed by your skin.
(Bernadette:)That's why you've been
all bloated and moody
(Bernadette:)and a giant pain in the ass.
You're full of estrogen
and you don't act like that.
(Bernadette:)That's 'cause I'm a woman. I've had
years of practice riding the dragon.